<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>托福学术写作练笔</title>
    <link href="/2023/12/28/writting/"/>
    <url>/2023/12/28/writting/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>托福改革后学术写作部分的个人练笔资料，题目来源于ETS官网的例题，仅供参考。</p></blockquote><h1 id="Targeted-Advertising"><a href="#Targeted-Advertising" class="headerlink" title="Targeted Advertising"></a>Targeted Advertising</h1><p>Personally speaking, I think targeted advertising is actually an ethical and acceptable way for marketing. I totally agree with Mike’s standpoint that this method is a cheaper and efficient for both consumers and companies. Additionally, I’d like to mention that it is really easy for any consumer who wants to omit targeted advertisements, since a policy forces websites to design their privacy settings so conspicuous that even a novice can find the right place to shut them down. Jessica, however, provided an alternative perspective that companies should concentrate on making more appealing and suitable advertisements. Yet she overlooked that the audiences who receive the ad possess their own biases and diversified interests that cannot simply be satisfied by a single ad at a time. As a result, entrepreneurs have to invest more money on ad making, rather than ameliorate the quality of their products, which undermines consumers’ welfare as well.</p><h1 id="Attractive-rural-areas"><a href="#Attractive-rural-areas" class="headerlink" title="Attractive rural areas:"></a>Attractive rural areas:</h1><h2 id="1"><a href="#1" class="headerlink" title="1"></a>1</h2><p>Personally speaking, I think more recreational businesses should be a top priority in building attractive rural areas. I firmly agree with Kelly’s idea that most people find urban centers appealing because they can enjoy many entertainment facilities there. Additionally, I should also mention that such cultural and recreational businesses can yield substantial income, which will ameliorate the development of local economy. As a result, more and more people will be gathered to such areas for economical reasons. Claire, however, provided an alternative perspective that the government should invest more financial aids to local farmers. Yet agriculture alone can not be the chief impetus for the development of local economy and the major generator for new jobs. For example, a modern farm can only create 10 jobs at most, an amusement park, by contrast, can generate at least 50 new jobs available. </p><h2 id="2"><a href="#2" class="headerlink" title="2"></a>2</h2><p>In my opinion, local governments should subsidize more recreational businesses in rural regions. I wholeheartedly endorse Kelly’s perspective that entertainment businesses can attract more citizens to enjoy their lives in remote areas. Furthermore, I’d like to add that local governments can procure more tax revenue by establishing recreational companies. Because many businesses like restaurants, amusement parks, or local shops are very lucrative and profitable, governments can use these monetary profits to improve local infrastructure. With the development of the rural regions’ construction, more and more people will migrate to that area. While Claire argues that financial aid in agriculture can spur more people to move to such areas, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. Modern farms can not be the main generator of new jobs as recreational companies. Thus fewer people will migrate to rural regions to work on farms.</p><h1 id="Grading-students"><a href="#Grading-students" class="headerlink" title="Grading students"></a>Grading students</h1><h2 id="1-1"><a href="#1-1" class="headerlink" title="1"></a>1</h2><p>Personally speaking, I think grading is an outdated way to judge a student and we should not use it anymore. I fully endorse and support Lila’s idea that grades can create an overly competitive environment where students feel anxious and insecure. Additionally, it is worth noting that grades can lead to a focus on test-taking strategies, and as a result, students may not even fully engage with academic materials. Thus a student’s learning efficiency can never be ameliorated or improved. Jake provides an alternative perspective that grades can help to measure students’ progress and identify specific areas where students are weak. However, such a claim faces many fallacies. For example, a student may lack the basic ability to communicate, yet in the current grading system he can still achieve a high score and his true problem may never be revealed.</p><h2 id="2-1"><a href="#2-1" class="headerlink" title="2"></a>2</h2><p>In my personal opinion, the traditional grading system is outdated and should be reconsidered. I completely endorse Lila’s perspective that grades can generate an overly competitive environment, leading to student anxiety and insecurity. Furthermore, relying heavily on grades may deter students from fully engaging with the academic material and solely focusing on test-taking strategies. Consequently, this can limit a student’s overall learning efficiency and impede their growth. While Jake contends that grades can be useful in measuring progress and identifying weaknesses, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with this claim. For instance, a student’s ability to communicate effectively may go unnoticed, allowing them to achieve high grades without addressing their underlying problem. Therefore, alternative assessment methods that provide a more comprehensive evaluation of students’ abilities and encourage holistic learning should be considered.</p><h2 id="3"><a href="#3" class="headerlink" title="3"></a>3</h2><p>In my personal opinion, assessment criteria should be only based on a student’s performance. I completely endorse Kelly’s perspective that it would be unfair to give a diligent student’s incorrect work a better grade. Furthermore, I’d add that such criteria are still effective when students move on to the next stage of their lives. Because companies will only focus on the outcome, not the process. Thus, students need to learn how to ameliorate the quality of their work instead of boasting about their hard work. While Paul contends that prioritizing hard work can be beneficial in cultivating a student’s character, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with his claim. For instance, though diligence is worthy of encouragement, effort does not equal accomplishment. And if a student can not complete a better result, his effort would be meaningless and futile.</p><h1 id="Gap-year"><a href="#Gap-year" class="headerlink" title="Gap year"></a>Gap year</h1><p>In my personal opinion, taking a gap year can be a beneficial option. I completely endorse Andrew’s perspective that students can seize the time and investigate various fields that are related to their future development. Furthermore, I would add that by meticulously scrutinizing oneself during the gap year, students can identify what they really like or who they want to be, leading to a more profound and meaningful impact on their growth. While Claire contends that the exorbitant tuition and other expenditures may impede a student from starting a costly gap year, it is crucial to recognize that the first-hand experiences and potential merits brought by the gap year are significant and essential. Once we notice the value of the gap year, we will find it not so costly.</p><h1 id="Urban-area"><a href="#Urban-area" class="headerlink" title="Urban area"></a>Urban area</h1><p>In my personal opinion, the urban space should be exploited more for green spaces and parks. While hospitals and health facilities mentioned by Kelly or businesses and commercial places put forth by Claire do count for people, I still believe that citizens do need green spaces desperately. With the development of industrial and the sprawling of urban areas, green spaces are rare in modern cities, and there are no alternative places for citizens to appreciate the beauty of nature and breathe the fresh air. What’s more, as the saying goes, “no man is an island”, and it is worth noting that many animals and plants are living in urban areas with general people. Thus those parks are the most suitable places for them to survive and even flourish.</p><h1 id="Training-employee"><a href="#Training-employee" class="headerlink" title="Training employee"></a>Training employee</h1><p>In my personal opinion, providing employee training is beneficial for both the company and employees. I completely endorse Kelly’s perspective that investing in training can make employees feel more valued by the company and bolster the relationship between employees and employers. Furthermore, I’d like to add that after receiving the training, employees will focus on honing their skills to express their gratitude to the employer. Thus, the company’s overall efficiency will be ameliorated, contributing to a more lucrative and profitable development mode. While Andrew contends that it seems more reasonable to hire the most skilled workers in the first place, it is crucial to recognize the fallacies associated with his claim. Those skilled workers, who lack a basic emotional relationship with the company, are more inclined to leave the employer than those who received training.</p><h1 id="Computer-learning"><a href="#Computer-learning" class="headerlink" title="Computer learning"></a>Computer learning</h1><h2 id="1-2"><a href="#1-2" class="headerlink" title="1"></a>1</h2><p>In my personal opinion, young children can not regard(rely on) educational digital games as a chief way to study. I completely endorse Andrew’s perspective that traditional teaching methods can exert a more beneficial impact on young children. Furthermore, I’d add that the interaction between parents and kids is so essential that it can not be simply replaced by computer games. Admittedly, computers can complete many onerous educational tasks, but what they will not achieve is the warmth of human interaction and gentle touch. While Kelly contends that since computers are pervasive(ubiquitous&#x2F;omnipresent) in the modern world, kids should explore them as early as possible, it is crucial to recognize the fallacies associated with her claim. For instance, early access to computers may lead to many ailments, like eye strain or arthritis, affecting young children’s growth(which can hinder young children’s growth).</p><h2 id="2-2"><a href="#2-2" class="headerlink" title="2"></a>2</h2><p>In my personal opinion, children should have access to computers and play educational digital games as early as possible. I completely endorse Kelly’s perspective that since computers are ubiquitous in the modern world, exploring computers via educational games would be beneficial for young children’s growth. Furthermore, multimedia information is an essential way for teaching, and the earlier the kids are exposed to the computer, the better they can adapt to future classes. And they can absorb fresh information and comprehensive knowledge from the internet, cultivating their study abilities. While Andrew contends that traditional ways like reading books are more effective in teaching children, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with his claim. For instance, when children move on to the next stage of their academic lives, they will feel confused and frustrated because they just do not understand everything about how to manipulate computers and how to utilize online resources to enrich their minds.</p><h1 id="Future-working"><a href="#Future-working" class="headerlink" title="Future working:"></a>Future working:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, people will enjoy more leisure time in the future. I completely endorse Claire’s perspective that once the overall standard of living has improved, wealthier people do not need to work as hard as contemporary workers. Furthermore, I’d add that the development of technology should be another factor that contributes to creating more free time. New technologies like artificial intelligence bring about a trend of using computers and advanced machines to replace human labor, which can also provide new jobs that entail more leisure time. Thus, twenty years in the future, workers will definitely possess more free time. While Paul contends that based on the nature of the economic system, companies tend to push workers to complete more assignments, it is necessary to point out the potential fallacies of his claim. For example, companies will be more willing to utilize new technologies to yield more products instead of pushing workers.</p><h1 id="Air-pollution"><a href="#Air-pollution" class="headerlink" title="Air pollution:"></a>Air pollution:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, providing financial support to electric cars and their customers is more beneficial. I completely endorse Paul’s perspective that driving cars may be the only option for people living in rural areas, and it is wise to support more electric cars to reduce carbon dioxide emissions brought by driving. Furthermore, I’d add that technology in producing electric cars is so advanced that such cars can be manufactured on a large scale and at a rapid rate. Thus, investing in electric car producers will certainly meet the demand of customers. While Claire contends that public transportation can reduce the amount of cars running on the road, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. Public transportation, though can hold many passengers, still produces carbon dioxide emissions. Yet an electric car using clean energy is completely environmentally friendly.</p><h1 id="Rural-area’s-economy"><a href="#Rural-area’s-economy" class="headerlink" title="Rural area’s economy:"></a>Rural area’s economy:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, promoting tourism is more beneficial to remote regions and it should be prioritized by local governments. I completely endorse Andrew’s perspective that rural areas’ standard of living can be improved in this way. Furthermore, I’d add that local governments can seize this opportunity and establish more tourism companies, which can not only ameliorate the situation of the local economy but generate new jobs available for residents as well. Thus it can achieve a more balanced development mode of our nation. While Claire contends that investing in agriculture or other industries will be more effective, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. What she omits is that rural areas have spent exorbitant expenditures in enhancing industry and agriculture, but proved to be fruitless and futile. Yet many other cases have shown that tourism can have a more profound and successful impact on a region’s economy.</p><h1 id="Rental-apartments-x2F-buying-housing"><a href="#Rental-apartments-x2F-buying-housing" class="headerlink" title="Rental apartments&#x2F;buying housing"></a>Rental apartments&#x2F;buying housing</h1><p>In my personal opinion, constructing more public rental apartments is the best way to alleviate a housing shortage in my country. I completely endorse Claire’s perspective that renting houses downtown can drastically shorten workers’ commuting time, contributing to their comfortable lives. Furthermore, I’d like to add that rental properties in big cities are often located in close proximity to public transportation, restaurants, entertainment venues, and job centers.<br>These can also provide convenient access to amenities and improve workers’ living standards. While Paul contends that houses in rural regions are quieter and more private, attracting more workers from cities, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with his claim. The tranquil life in rural areas is at the expense of excessive expenditures in housing. For example, buyers of those houses are responsible for property maintenance and renovations, which is highly costly and exorbitant.</p><h1 id="Judging-a-teacher："><a href="#Judging-a-teacher：" class="headerlink" title="Judging a teacher："></a>Judging a teacher：</h1><p>In my personal opinion, students’ feedback in testing is more important in judging a teacher’s professional ability. I completely endorse Kelly’s perspective that students’ scores in exams can reflect a teacher’s job performance objectively. Furthermore, I’d like to add that questionnaires with contents like whether a student is satisfied with his or her teacher, and what part of a class is the most confusing and obscure, are also valid in measuring a teacher’s performance. By filling out such questionnaires, students can express their attitude toward a teacher’s performance, providing additional information. While Andrew contends that experienced teachers are more capable of determining a teacher’s ability, for they are equipped with professional knowledge, it is crucial to recognize the fallacies associated with his claim. Unlike students who are unsophisticated and naive, experienced teachers may have personal relationships or emotional inclinations, leading to conclusions based on bias and not credible in judging a teacher’s performance impartially.</p><h1 id="Field-trips"><a href="#Field-trips" class="headerlink" title="Field trips:"></a>Field trips:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, field trips can benefit children’s education. I completely endorse Paul’s perspective that field trips have a positive impact on children’s career development, contributing to their growth. Furthermore, I’d like to add that by providing chances for kids to have access to observe and even manipulate tangible exhibits, children can have a different view toward knowledge. For example, some museums are equipped with facilities that are both educational and recreational, enabling children to interact with them and experience ancient life. Thus children can grasp more academic knowledge than they can gain from test books. While Kelly contends that the onerous tasks for teachers to plan a field trip may exhaust their efforts in class teaching, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. In fact, teachers can hire professional companies to help them design a field trip, reducing their tasks.</p><h1 id="Graduate-working"><a href="#Graduate-working" class="headerlink" title="Graduate working:"></a>Graduate working:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, large, established companies are more suitable for a graduate to begin working. I completely endorse Kelly’s perspective that by working for venerated firms, graduates can receive valuable experiences, enhancing the persuasiveness of their resumes. Furthermore, I’d like to add that large corporations also provide employees with professional training, enabling graduates to accumulate experience and gain more practical knowledge. As a result, graduates can not only be familiar with their work but hone their skills as well. While Andrew contends that new, innovative companies can attract graduates, spurring young people to be more energetic, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with his claim. Like the graduate, those new firms lack experience and may mislead young people to the wrong path in their career development.</p><h1 id="Retaining-workers"><a href="#Retaining-workers" class="headerlink" title="Retaining workers:"></a>Retaining workers:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, improving employees’ professional skills is an optimal choice for companies to retain their employees. I completely endorse Claire’s perspective that offering chances for workers to hone their skills can definitely make employees feel confident and energetic. Furthermore, I’d like to add that corporations can also encourage employees from different departments to communicate and interact with each other frequently, which can not only enhance their emotional links but help improve their professional skills as well. Consequently, employees can forge an emotional bond with the company, leading to healthier employer-employee relationships. While Paul contends that creating a well-furnished workplace can help ameliorate employee’s working conditions, contributing to retaining workers, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with his claim. Employees’ moods are mostly affected by their professional issues, not the tangible environment. And improving their working skills can better solve this problem and keep them from leaving.</p><h1 id="Journal-writing"><a href="#Journal-writing" class="headerlink" title="Journal writing:"></a>Journal writing:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, journal writing is not worthwhile to support teaching. I completely endorse Paul’s perspective that since students already have onerous tasks in different courses, journal writing can be regarded as an excessive burden to them. Furthermore, I’d like to add that the majority of students live a tedious life, and they do not have numerous novel things to record. Thus students may soon find that their resources for writing journals will be depleted, and they may even try to make fake records, which will undermine their credibility. While Claire contends that journal writing enables students to hone their writing skills, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. Because students’ journals are assignments, not their own wishes, they may not write the material genuinely, contributing nothing valuable to teachers.</p><h1 id="Attend-classes"><a href="#Attend-classes" class="headerlink" title="Attend classes:"></a>Attend classes:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, class attendance policies are essential and should not be replaced by optional attendance policies. I completely endorse Andrew’s perspective that learning to obey class attendance policies in university is beneficial for students when they move on to the next stage of their lives. Furthermore, I’d like to add that some profound information and instrumental knowledge can not be gained outside classes. For instance, professors may use their personal experiences in demonstrating some professional terms, and give students their insights about some issues, allowing students to explore more academic fields. If students miss such classes, they may easily omit this information. While Claire contends that if students have understood some knowledge, they do not need to attend some classes, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. Taking classes is the most efficient approach to absorbing new knowledge comprehensively. And they may miss some important details if they attend classes occasionally.  </p><h1 id="Part-time-jobs"><a href="#Part-time-jobs" class="headerlink" title="Part-time jobs:"></a>Part-time jobs:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, part-time jobs are essential in children’s development. I completely endorse Claire’s perspective that participating in part-time jobs can foster a child’s time management skills. Furthermore, I’d like to add that part-time jobs can also provide kids a chance to enhance their monetary awareness. For instance, adolescents can learn how to manage the money they gained from work, allocating money equally in fields like study, recreation, and diet. As a result, they can cultivate their own financial management abilities which are important when they move on to the next stage of their lives. While Andrew contends that schoolwork is so vital that kids should prioritize academic learning over part-time jobs, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with his claim. Students can only do their part-time jobs using their extracurricular time. Far from impeding their academic learning, students actually can gain more instrumental and practical knowledge from their part-time jobs, which is highly valuable. </p><h1 id="Senior-x2F-younger-employees"><a href="#Senior-x2F-younger-employees" class="headerlink" title="Senior&#x2F;younger employees:"></a>Senior&#x2F;younger employees:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, younger employees should not be encouraged to mentor senior coworkers. I completely endorse Kelly’s perspective that senior coworkers who are more experienced and professional can impart useful information to younger employees. Furthermore, I’d like to add that younger workers lack the ability to communicate as patiently as senior coworkers, and they may feel frustrated and even irascible when senior workers do not understand the knowledge conveyed by younger workers, contributing to a tighter and worse relationship between younger and senior employees. Thus younger workers may not be suitable for teaching senior coworkers. While Claire contends that young workers are more familiar with advanced technology, necessitating senior coworkers to learn from them, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. Senior coworkers are still capable of searching for essential information online and absorbing new knowledge independently. </p><h1 id="Job-aid"><a href="#Job-aid" class="headerlink" title="Job aid:"></a>Job aid:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, governments should support job training courses to address this issue. I completely endorse Andrew’s perspective that making expensive training programs available to general people can hone their professional skills, enabling them to be recruited. Furthermore, I’d like to add that by attending such classes, people will feel more confident about themselves, releasing their stress and anxiety. Consequently, the social environment will be more peaceful since everyone is enthusiastic about their future career development. While Kelly contends that providing people with financial aid will ameliorate their current situation, allowing them to get through difficult times, I am still concerned about the potential fallacies associated with her claim. Nowadays many young people can receive financial support from their families, and their major problem is worrying about finding a job. Thus governments need to offer them professional instructions and training instead of monetary aid.</p><h1 id="Teacher-taking-courses"><a href="#Teacher-taking-courses" class="headerlink" title="Teacher taking courses:"></a>Teacher taking courses:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, teachers must take courses every few years. I completely endorse Andrew’s perspective that teachers should update their knowledge and absorb new academic advancements. Furthermore, I’d like to add that if teachers are equipped with fresh academic knowledge, they can have a profound impact on their students. Because they can combine new academic developments with novel examples, attracting adolescents to appreciate the beauty of the knowledge and cultivate their creativity. As a result, the whole class’s study environment will be ameliorated and improved. While Claire contends that participating in such courses will occupy teachers’ time, making them feel bored, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. Since teachers have more vacations than general occupations, they can utilize their extracurricular time to attend such courses, which will not affect their regular schedules. Thus their daily work will not be interfered with.</p><h1 id="Family-working"><a href="#Family-working" class="headerlink" title="Family working:"></a>Family working:</h1><p>In my personal opinion, working together is beneficial for enhancing the bonds among family members. I wholeheartedly endorse Andrew’s perspective that collaborating towards the same goal can foster communication and interactions within the family, ultimately creating a more harmonious family environment. Furthermore, I’d like to add that shared events can have a profound impact on the younger generation, as they can gain more knowledge and skills from their elder relatives. For instance, when children are actively engaged in household chores and cooking alongside their parents, they become more independent and mature. While Claire argues that since family members have diversified viewpoints, they are hard to find a suitable activity to work together, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. When working together, even seemingly mundane tasks can become engaging to everyone when approached as a team.</p><h1 id="Cinemas"><a href="#Cinemas" class="headerlink" title="Cinemas:"></a>Cinemas:</h1><p>In my opinion, cinemas will exist in the future. I wholeheartedly endorse Paul’s perspective that going to theaters or cinemas to watch performances has been rooted in human culture and has been entrenched for thousands of years. Furthermore, I’d like to add that cinema provides audiences with multiple sensory stimulation, which one can not gain from one’s own home using smartphones or televisions. For instance, giant screens can expand audiences’ sight, which can not only enable them to enjoy fascinating scenes but also offer chances for directors to improvise and create more imaginative plots. While Claire argues that films in the future do not need such a wide screen to show, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. Directors still need more rooms to create their plots, increasing their works’ quality.</p><h1 id="Museums"><a href="#Museums" class="headerlink" title="Museums:"></a>Museums:</h1><p>In my opinion, museums’ most significant influence on citizens is offering them a chance to absorb new knowledge. I wholeheartedly endorse Andrew’s perspective that by appreciating the exhibits, people can be motivated and release their anxiety and stress. Furthermore, I’d like to add that museums can also impart people with knowledge about the nation, including content like how the country was established and how the regional culture emerged. By grasping those fascinating stories, people can cultivate a sense of patriotism. While Claire argues that museums’ major function is enhancing people’s sense of community, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. Museums were built because they were furnished with cultural exhibits, not volunteer jobs. Thus their goal is disseminating cultural knowledge instead of providing voluntary offers.</p><h1 id="Communication-skills"><a href="#Communication-skills" class="headerlink" title="Communication skills:"></a>Communication skills:</h1><p>In my opinion, advanced communication skills are an essential skill that every successful leader should have. I wholeheartedly endorse Andrew’s perspective that if leaders can clearly express their goals and plans to employees, the whole company can work efficiently. Furthermore, I’d like to add that excellent communication skills can also help address convoluted issues associated with workers’ conflicts. For instance, a wise leader has a direct insight toward the core problem of the conflict, explaining the pros and cons fluently to their workers. Thus employees can recognize the truth and be glad to receive their boss’s advice. As a result, great communication skills contribute to a harmonious environment in the company. While Kelly emphasizes the importance of a profound understanding of the business, I still hold the belief that communication skills should weigh more. Because bosses can have professional workers to deal with such problems and give them suggestions, it is unnecessary for employers to have such skills.</p><h1 id="Environment"><a href="#Environment" class="headerlink" title="Environment:"></a>Environment:</h1><p>In my opinion, promoting the economy is important, but not at the expense of the environment. I wholeheartedly endorse Kelly’s perspective that constant environmental damage can lead to an unprecedented environmental catastrophe. Furthermore, I’d like to add that current environmental problems are so serious that we should take instant action. For example, the average height of water floors in Africa has been dwindling for 50 years, and if we fail to stop this trend, a regional freshwater shortage will affect local people’s lives. Thus governments should enact laws to protect the environment as quickly as possible. While Paul argues that expanding industries can create more jobs for general people, increasing their living standards, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with his claim. By meticulously scrutinizing the pros and cons, we can draw a result that industries have already reached a summit level in human history. If we reduce some of the factories and invest more money in environmentally friendly companies, it will not undermine economic growth at all.</p><h1 id="Public-transportation"><a href="#Public-transportation" class="headerlink" title="Public transportation:"></a>Public transportation:</h1><p>In my opinion, supporting free public transportation with tax revenue is beneficial. I wholeheartedly endorse Paul’s perspective that considering the latent pros brought by free public transportation, it is worth allocating tax revenue to this. Furthermore, I’d like to add that I have read in an article that if 100,000 people choose to use public transportation as their major approach for commuting, the average carbon dioxide emissions per year in Tokyo can dwindle by 10%, which is a persuasive enough number to emphasize the importance of promoting free public transportation. While Kelly argues that charging tax for public transportation will increase citizens’ financial burden, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with her claim. If people refuse to pay taxes for public transportation and insist on driving cars, the environmental problems will be worse. As a result, people need to spend more money on health problems.</p><h1 id="Buying-tech-products"><a href="#Buying-tech-products" class="headerlink" title="Buying tech products:"></a>Buying tech products:</h1><p>In my opinion, the biggest mistake that people make when purchasing tech products is they always buy things that do not conform to their actual needs. I wholeheartedly endorse Claire’s perspective that people can wrongly pay exorbitant costs for tech products’ features that they hardly use. Furthermore, I’d like to add that some merchandising methods should be clarified to general people, otherwise, they may repeatedly fall into the same trap. For instance, smartphone producers can propagate ideas that their products have improved their butteries this year, misleading many consumers to buy their phones. Those customers do not need such advanced tech. While Paul argues that software that a consumer uses should match with the hardware they purchased, it is crucial to recognize the potential fallacies associated with his claim. Nowadays the majority of software can meet the needs of the hardware, and such problems occur less frequently than before.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>英语学习</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>托福</tag>
      
      <tag>写作</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>托福学术写作素材</title>
    <link href="/2023/12/28/toefl/"/>
    <url>/2023/12/28/toefl/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p>托福改革后学术写作部分的资料素材，按照几个不同的话题展开</p></blockquote><h1 id="话题一：保护环境"><a href="#话题一：保护环境" class="headerlink" title="话题一：保护环境"></a>话题一：保护环境</h1><p>【1】industrial development<br>【2】serious <font color=Red>ailments</font>（an illness, typically a minor one) 可以替换为：<font color=Red>malady</font>（maladies）<br>【3】表示疾病：cancer&#x2F;lung disease&#x2F;flu&#x2F;fever&#x2F;<font color=Red>diarrhea</font>（腹泻）&#x2F;allergy（过敏）&#x2F;diabetes（糖尿病）&#x2F;hypertension（糖尿病）&#x2F;arthritis（关节炎）&#x2F;Pneumonia（肺炎）<br>【4】These sorts of illness can be a real <font color=Red>strain<br></font> on our medical systems.<br>【5】For example, it could take decades for an innovative company to create a clean energy source, but people are suffering from <font color=Red>environmental catastrophes</font> right now.<br>【6】We only have one planet and if we don’t take care of it, we won’t have pleasant lives in the future.<br>【7】Economic growth can be important, but not at the expense of the environment.<br>【8】I think we need to shift towards more environmentally-friendly economic practices,<br> such as investing in renewable energy and promoting environmentally-friendly technologies.<br> <strong>Renewable energy 举例：</strong><br>Renewable energy refers to energy sources that can be <font color=Red>replenished naturally</font> and are considered sustainable.<br><em>Solar energy</em>: it involves <font color=Red>harnessing</font> the power of the sun using PV panels to convert sunlight into electricity.<br><em>Wind energy</em>: capture the <font color=Red>kinetic</font> energy of the wind and <font color=Red>convert it into electrical energy.</font><br><em>Hydropower</em>: it utilizes the energy of moving water, such as <font color=Red>tidal currents</font>, to generate electricity.<br><em>Biomass energy</em><br><em>Ocean energy</em><br>These examples highlight the wide range of renewable energy sources available, each with its own unique characteristics and applications, contributing to a more sustainable and cleaner energy future.<br><strong>Renewable energy 的反义词：</strong><br>fossil energy&#x2F;non-renewable energy, coal, petroleum, natural gas, geothermal energy, nuclear power<br>Due to the increasing <font color=Red>consumption</font> of non-renewable energy like petroleum and the urgency of improving the ecological environment, energy conservation became a hot topic in the world.<br>The country are facing a huge problem that is the energy crisis, with the continuous exploitation of the non-renewable energy such as coal, oil, natural gas.<br>The <font color=Red>dwindling</font> availability of non-renewable resources like oil and coal necessitates proactive measures and the development of alternative plans for a sustainable energy future.<br><strong>Proactive：积极的，主动的</strong><br>Among these <font color=Red>alternatives</font>, solar energy <font color=Red>stands out as a promising solution</font>. By enhancing our current methods of harnessing sunlight and converting it into electricity more efficiently, we can decrease our reliance on fossil fuels. Prioritizing the adoption of solar energy provides a viable pathway to protect our planet and mitigate potential environmental catastrophes.”<br>表示“利用，使用”：<br>utilize&#x2F;harness<br>【9】We will all live much healthier if the world around us is clean.<br>【10】environmental sustainability<br>【11】It would be fatal for the nation to overlook the urgency of this situation.<br>【12】Steps have to be taken to mitigate and <font color=Red>ameliorate</font> problems.<br>【13】Now water tables <font color=Red>plummet</font> in countries <font color=Red>harboring</font> half the world’s population.</p><h1 id="话题二：健康"><a href="#话题二：健康" class="headerlink" title="话题二：健康"></a>话题二：健康</h1><p>【1】reduce the prevalence of serious health problems in society.<br>【2】I read that budget of our national health care system has increased by 20% in the last five years alone. I was shocked when I read that.<br>【3】make healthy choices more affordable.<br>【4】For example, they could <font color=Red>subsidize</font> （资助，补助）products like fresh fruit and vegetables.<br>【5】I think people would be more willing to buy carrots and apples <font color=Red>if they were cheaper</font>.<br>【6】have access to clean drinking water, <font color=Red>sanitation systems</font> (公共卫生系统), and <font color=Red>free vaccines</font> that have dramatically reduced health problems.<br>【7】public health campaigns have helped educate people about healthy habits such as exercise, healthy eating, and about the danger of smoking.<br>(<font color=Red>Public health campaign</font>【公共卫生运动】：public health campaigns about healthy eating and exercise have improved our lives.<br><font color=Red>Prevention is always better than cure</font> and our public health campaigns on drinking and obesity reflects this.<br>【8】for example, although children are less likely to have physical education classes or play outside nowadays, they still suffer from fewer diseases than in the past.<br>【9】<font color=Red>exercise regimen</font> 锻炼计划<br>例句：Daily builds, like a daily exercise regimen, is typically accepted as a best practice.<br>【10】The <font color=Red>exorbitant&#x2F;excessive</font> cost of our health-insurance benefits reflects the high dollar amount of medical expenses incurred by general people.<br>【11】some people remain <font color=Red>inveterate</font> smokers.<br>【12】but habits <font color=Red>ingrained</font> by tradition can be hard to break.<br>【13】Fairness in access to care and efficiency in service delivery were <font color=Red>overarching</font> goals.<br>【14】addressing this issue requires <font color=Red>unanimous</font> agreement and <font color=Red>steadfast enforcement</font> throughout the world.</p><h1 id="话题三：商业贸易"><a href="#话题三：商业贸易" class="headerlink" title="话题三：商业贸易"></a>话题三：商业贸易</h1><p>【1】<font color=Red>opt-out</font>：退出<br>【2】<font color=Red>user- friendly</font><br>【3】Society is more <font color=Red>diverse</font> than ever before, so it is almost impossible to create messages that everyone finds attractive.<br>【4】go out of business：倒闭 &#x3D; go into <font color=Red>liquidation</font> &#x3D; go bankrupt<br>【5】budget<br>【6】wealthy individuals<br>【7】nowadays people’s <font color=Red>purchasing decisions</font> are mostly based on cost.<br>【8】Many people prefer to buy the cheapest products available, even if they are sold by <font color=Red>unethical</font> companies.<br>【9】Because the <font color=Red>economic recession</font> remains deeply entrenched, they just can not afford to think about businesses’ reputation when they are shopping.<br>【10】economic growth is the only way to solve many of the social and economic problems we face.<br>【11】We need a strong economy to create jobs, reduce <font color=Red>poverty</font>, and improve standards of living.<br>【12】Not only that, but when companies grow stronger and more profitable, they can develop new technologies that solve our environmental problems.<br>【13】lucrative<br>【14】dwindle<br>【15】Many policy makers insist that consumer spending is a strong economic <font color=Red>catalyst</font> and, therefore, a <font color=Red>paucity</font> of retail stores is a contributing factor to low-performing economies.<br>【16】They could even <font color=Red>exacerbate</font> some flaws in the economy.</p><h1 id="话题四：科技"><a href="#话题四：科技" class="headerlink" title="话题四：科技"></a>话题四：科技</h1><p>【1】it is extremely easy to do this nowadays, as Internet browsers are very user-friendly.<br>【2】Even people that are <font color=Red>inexperienced</font> with technology can find the right settings and adjust them.<br>【3】cope with and recover from such problems.<br>【4】help us deal with many serious problems currently affecting society.<br>【5】AI has already been used to make driving safer and reduce car accidents, so we already have some <font color=Red>proof</font> that AI is helping people around world.<br>【6】According to <font color=Red>statistics</font> I read last week, <font color=Red>self-driving cars</font> get in accidents 80% less frequently than cars driven by humans. That seems an incredible advantage to me.<br>【7】eliminate certain jobs.<br>【8】For example, when new products are invented using AI they still have to be <font color=Red>manufactured</font>, which means that new factory jobs are created.<br>【9】Not only that, but AI learning tools can help people increase&#x2F;hone their skills and make themselves more attractive employees for various companies.<br>【10】new scientist discoveries.<br>【11】technology has led to <font color=Red>substantive breakthroughs</font>.&#x2F;marked a quantum leap forward in the fight against diseases.<br>【12】new technology also makes it a lot easier for doctors to <font color=Red>deliver those treatments</font>.<br>【13】In many cases, doctors can assist patients over the Internet ( &#x3D; internet), from miles away.<br>【14】That wasn’t possible when my parents were young.<br>【15】Back then, the <font color=Red>average life expectancy</font> was much lower than it is now.<br>(The average life expectancy 用法：The average life expectancy is up from 35 to 73 years. Illiteracy rate 【<font color=Red>illiteracy rate: 文盲率】</font> is down from 80% to below 3.5%)<br>【16】It is always <font color=Red>futile</font> to try to hold back the progress of history.<br>【17】Information on it is <font color=Red>scant</font>.</p><h1 id="话题五：学习"><a href="#话题五：学习" class="headerlink" title="话题五：学习"></a>话题五：学习</h1><p>【1】create an <font color=Red>overly competitive</font> environment and may not accurately <font color=Red>reflect</font> a student’s progress.<br>【2】grades can lead to a focus on <font color=Red>test-taking strategies</font> rather than actual learning, and as a result students may not fully <font color=Red>engage with the material</font>.<br>【3】This means they could lack key knowledge that they will need when they <font color=Red>move on to the next stage of their academic life</font>.<br>【4】<font color=Red>identify</font> the specific areas where students are weak.<br>【5】investing in libraries can help <font color=Red>recruit</font> and <font color=Red>retain</font> the most talented professors, which can ultimately benefit the university as a whole.<br>【6】attract the best possible students, which improves the whole <font color=Red>academic environment</font>.<br>Everyone enjoys classes a lot when their classmates are intelligent and devoted to their studies.<br>【7】For example, they could look at a student’s essay, see that (if) he is weak (when it comes to) grammar, and tell him that in person&#x2F;face to face.<br>【8】online courses make education more accessible. For one, they help reduce <font color=Red>commuting time and costs</font> and give students more flexibility in their schedules.<br>online learning can be more <font color=Red>accessible</font> for students who have disabilities or live far away from campus.<br>【9】Traditionally, high costs have prevented many people from <font color=Red>pursuing an education</font>, but thanks to online classes, cost is less of a problem.<br>【10】when we take classes in person, it is easier to build relationships and collaborate on group projects.<br>【11】we learn just as much from personal connections as we do from our actual lectures and textbooks.<br>【12】it is a lot easier to <font color=Red>get distracted</font> when we study at home using our personal computers.<br>【13】the main expense for students is <font color=Red>tuition</font>, and universities charge the same amount for online classes and offline classes .<br>多种教学模式的名称：distance self-study, online collective teaching, online one-on-one tutoring, offline classroom teaching, tuition-free learning, blended online&#x2F;offline programs.<br>【14】I can learn better when I am actively engaged with academic material and can exchange ideas with my classmates.<br>【15】When I have the opportunity to <font color=Red>get immediate feedback</font>, I can understand things more deeply.<br>【16】I also benefit from hearing about different perspectives and new ways of thinking about challenging topics.<br>【17】Discussions help me retain the information better since they are more interactive and memorable.<br>【18】With lectures, there is usually a clear structure and a <font color=Red>set agenda</font>, which can help me stay focused and organized.<br>【19】Being able to take notes and study at my own pace. I can not do those things if I have to engage in a discussion.<br>【20】Not only that, but discussions can sometimes <font color=Red>get off track</font> （偏离轨道，跑题）or become too <font color=Red>argumentative&#x2F;contentious&#x2F;polemic</font>, which can take away from&#x2F;undermine learning experience.<br><strong>跑题：stray from the topic&#x2F;digress from the subject</strong><br>【21】interactive classes are much better than ones where we just sit and passively listen to a professor.<br>【22】we need to prepare for discussions in advance, which also improves our retention （记忆力）of specific details and concepts.<br>【23】improve our grades on tests and assignments.<br>【24】If we need to take notes about things we missed, we can just listen to a recording and <font color=Red>fill in the blanks （自己推测，填补信息）</font>.<br>【25】As a result, we can take part in the <font color=Red>cut and thrust of debate （针锋相对的辩论）</font>and not worry about missing anything critical （重要的）.<br><strong>重要：significant&#x2F;vital&#x2F;crucial&#x2F;considerable&#x2F;major&#x2F;important&#x2F;momentous&#x2F;instrumental</strong><br>【26】While most parents, teachers and <font color=Red>clinicians</font> would react to an adolescent using drugs or getting drunk, they may easily overlook teenagers who are engaging in <font color=Red>inconspicuous</font> behaviors.<br>【27】The <font color=Red>excessive emphasis</font> on scholarship generates many <font color=Red>unread</font> books and <font color=Red>mediocre</font> articles in academic journals.<br>【28】under this system, people, no matter whether they are rich or poor, clever or foolish, have a chance to be educated at universities or colleges.<br>【28】<font color=Red>exacting&#x2F;demanding&#x2F;laborious&#x2F;onerous</font> tasks may <font color=Red>dampen&#x2F;dwindle</font> students’ enthusiasms<br>【29】Constant criticism is enough to <font color=Red>demoralize</font> anybody.<br>【30】Even elementary school students are complaining about homework fatigue.<br>【31】Many people believe that there’s no <font color=Red>shortcut</font> to success, and sometimes <font color=Red>dull</font> efforts are necessary.<br>【32】His poor method of learning by <font color=Red>rote</font> made him unable to deal with the problems in his work flexibly.<br>Rote memorization is an inefficient way to learn.<br>Education in high schools is still excessively stifling, rote and high pressured.<br>Rote memorization is based on the theory that if you look at information enough times, it will magically be stored inside your mind.<br>【33】Research now shows that regular quizzes, short essays, and other assignments over the course of a term better enhance learning and retention.<br>Visual material aids the retention of information.</p><h1 id="话题六：社交媒体"><a href="#话题六：社交媒体" class="headerlink" title="话题六：社交媒体"></a>话题六：社交媒体</h1><p>【1】it is almost impossible for most people to get their messages on television or in print media because those are controlled by companies and wealthy individuals.<br>【2】this sort of technology has had a <font color=Red>negative</font> impact on our ability to communicate face-to-face.<br>【3】People are too <font color=Red>reliant</font> on text messages, social media, and things like that, which can lead to a <font color=Red>lack of nuance and depth</font> in our interactions.<br><strong>Nuance:细微差别</strong><br>【4】It’s harder to <font color=Red>read body language and tone of voice over text</font>, and that can result in misunderstandings and miscommunications, or even conflicts.<br>Body language: In a conversation between two persons, 65% of communication is done through body language.<br>【5】If people want to become effective communicators, they should talk to people in person.<br>【6】Smartphones make it possible for us to stay connected with acquaintances and loved ones&#x2F;relatives who are far away, and social networks provide a platform for introverted people to express themselves in ways that they may not be able to do in person.<br>【7】certain group of people aren’t able to share their ideas in traditional media like newspapers and television broadcasts, but if they have smartphones they can easily do so by posting to social networks like Twitter and Facebook.<br>【8】By sharing their ideas, they can bring about positive changes in society.<br>【9】It is challenging to pick up on subtle details in online communication.<br>【10】Nowadays we can not only text messages, but also images and videos, which can add a lot of depth and nuance to our interactions.<br>【11】influencers have large followings and can <font color=Red>sway</font> （动摇）consumer behavior by <font color=Red>endorsing</font> （代言）products or services.<br>【12】When young people start admiring these influencers and trust their recommendations, they are more likely to buy products or services that they endorse.<br>【13】However, I also think there are some concerns about the <font color=Red>authenticity</font> of these endorsements, as some influencers may promote products that they don’t actually use or believe in.<br>【14】While they may have large followings, most people are smart enough to make their own purchasing decisions based on their needs and preferences.<br>【15】social media influencers aren’t as significant as some people suggest.<br>【16】people are too smart to be influenced by them.<br>【17】twenty years ago a <font color=Red>charismatic</font> person might have convinced us to buy something we didn’t really need, but I think that doesn’t happen so much nowadays.<br>【18】That’s because we can thoroughly search whatever products we are interested in using blogs, consumer magazines and social media.<br>【19】Since we can use these sources of information to find goods that exactly suit our needs, we aren’t swayed by the <font color=Red>exaggerated</font> claims of social media influencers.<br>【20】make <font color=Red>rash</font> decisions （草率的决定）about what to buy.<br>【21】In fact, some experts worry that if people become too paranoid about online privacy, it could have deleterious effects.<br>【22】What it will not achieve is the <font color=Red>warmth of human interaction and touch</font>.<br>【23】We still need the human touch or the human interaction, particularly when people are depressed.<br>【24】There are doubts whether people watching television, a “lean back” medium, crave interaction.<br><strong>Crave:渴望</strong><br>【25】Our <font color=Red>humanness arises out of</font> these relationships in the course of social interaction.</p><h1 id="话题七：政府投资"><a href="#话题七：政府投资" class="headerlink" title="话题七：政府投资"></a>话题七：政府投资</h1><p>【1】<font color=Red>infrastructure</font>: repairing roads and bridges, expanding public transportation, and improving <font color=Red>access to clean water and sanitation</font>.<br>When cities have good infrastructure it’s easier for residents to get around, and new businesses are attracted to the area.<br>They also experience fewer serious accidents.<br>Life is usually controlled by cars in the US. There is no cheap and good public transportation, so it is so difficult to get somewhere.<br>【2】social programs: the government could invest in things like education, <font color=Red>affordable housing</font>, and health care, which can help <font color=Red>address issues like poverty</font>, inequality, and access to basic needs.<br>By providing these types of services, the government can help improve people’s well-being.<br>These are things that everyone benefits from, unlike a road which is only used by people who drive cars.<br>The costs of things like childcare and housing are rapidly increasing nowadays, so government support is urgently needed.<br>Most people agree that it’s much easier for people to have jobs and raise families in cities with well-funded social programs.<br>Bad housing is <font color=Red>interconnected</font> with debt and poverty.<br>People have been <font color=Red>grumbling</font> about interest rates and housing prices for many years.<br>Cheap housing would <font color=Red>vastly</font> improve the living standards of ordinary people.<br>The basic problems of the <font color=Red>inner-city underclass</font> are inadequate housing and lack of jobs.<br>Rental yield in China is low, and does not justify buying a house to rent it out.<br>Public rental housing&#x2F;The introduction of a public rental housing is one solution.<br>Some rental properties include utilities in the rent, saving you the hassle of setting up and paying for separate utility bills.<br><strong>hassle：起哄，烦恼</strong><br>Renting can provide financial flexibility, as renters do not have to ftie up their savings in a down payment or other expenses. This allows workers to <font color=Red>allocate</font> their money to other investments or financial goals.<br><strong>tie up：捆绑，占用</strong><br><strong>down payment：首付</strong><br>Renters are generally not responsible for property maintenance and renovations. This frees up time and eliminates the stress of dealing with <font color=Red>home maintenance tasks</font>, allowing workers to focus on their careers and personal lives.<br>Rental properties in big cities are often located in <font color=Red>close proximity</font> to public transportation, restaurants, entertainment venues, and job centers. This provides convenient access to amenities and reduces commute times.<br><strong>Proximity：临近，接近</strong><br>So what if some of that financial largesse could be deployed within the surrounding city blocks, creating assets and new wealth within the underclass.<br><strong>largesse：慷慨的赠予</strong><br>surrounding city blocks：周边地区，郊区 &#x3D; <font color=Red>outskirts</font> &#x3D; suburb<br>【3】<font color=Red>philanthropy</font>: 慈善<br>Philanthropy can provide <font color=Red>immediate relief</font> to those in need and contribute to the overall well-being of society right away.<br>【4】address the <font color=Red>root causes</font> of serious social and environmental problems.<br>【5】By doing business in more responsible ways, companies can have a more meaningful and lasting&#x2F;profound impact on society.<br>【6】Moreover, if they <font color=Red>attract positive attention</font> from consumers&#x2F;customers they could inspire other companies to do the same.<br>【7】<font color=Red>charitable</font> donations are a way to quickly address the serious problems that we are facing.<br>【8】some of these problems - like <font color=Red>homelessness and food insecurity</font> - are more serious than they have ever been, so companies certainly <font color=Red>have a role to play</font>.<br>【9】Even a small donation can save someone’s life.<br>【10】China, in particular, has the <font color=Red>wherewithal</font> to make good on its promises of massive economic stimulus.<br>【11】形成循环：<br><strong>良性循环：virtuous cycle</strong><br>The goal here is to increase your motivation and ability to avoid distractions, and to ensure a virtuous cycle.<br><strong>恶性循环：vicious cycle</strong><br>Pessimists feared that if the rising population prevented the world’s poor from advancing, they would get caught in a vicious cycle of poverty and large families.<br>【12】This XXX has put the <font color=Red>spurs</font> to the city’s sluggish development process, and also shaken off a bit of government’s <font color=Red>hidebound</font> attitude about economy.</p><h1 id="话题八：工作"><a href="#话题八：工作" class="headerlink" title="话题八：工作"></a>话题八：工作</h1><p>【1】remote work is a very <font color=Red>positive trend</font>. When we work from home, we spend commuting （通勤）and we have more flexible schedules.<br>【2】productive<br>【3】Some people say this is because they aren’t <font color=Red>distracted</font> by their <font color=Red>coworkers&#x2F;colleagues</font>, while others suggest it’s because their energy isn’t drained during a long and <font color=Red>bothersome commute</font>.<br>【4】build relationships and collaborate effectively.<br>【5】limit our chances to <font color=Red>earn promotions and raises</font>.<br>【6】we fell much more comfortable in our own house, so we can think more creatively about our assigned tasks.<br>【7】Nowadays, <font color=Red>employers value</font> creativity <font color=Red>above all else</font>, so they ought to consider giving employees this option.<br>【8】For example, most professionals&#x2F;specialized persons use LinkedIn to keep in touch these days.<br>【9】In many websites like these are better ways to <font color=Red>socialize with people</font> in our field than talking to them in person.<br>在各自的地点：in our field&#x2F;At their respective locations<br>【10】they are convenient and make it really easy to share articles and videos relevant to our careers.<br>【11】Diligence is worthy of encouragement, but effort does not equal accomplishment.</p><p><strong>有益的：</strong><br>Beneficial&#x2F;salutary<br>They both have salutary and harmful aspects to the human health.<br>【12】Busyness is <font color=Red>antithetical</font> to creativity.<br>【13】Women have yet to achieve wage or occupational <font color=Red>parity</font> in many fields.</p><p><strong>享受：</strong><br>enjoy&#x2F;relish<br>I relish the challenge of doing jobs that others turn down.<br>Rather than seeing the unknown as a threat, relish it as a challenge.</p><h1 id="话题九：人际交往"><a href="#话题九：人际交往" class="headerlink" title="话题九：人际交往"></a>话题九：人际交往</h1><p>【1】Other people may give us <font color=Red>instrumental</font> support-financial aid, material resources, and <font color=Red>needed services</font>-that reduces stress by helping us resolve and cope with our problems.<br>【2】The genuine good friend is can <font color=Red>admonish</font> mutually.<br>【3】Admonish your friends in private, but praise them in public.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>英语学习</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>托福</tag>
      
      <tag>写作</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Tonight I Can Write</title>
    <link href="/2023/12/27/poem/"/>
    <url>/2023/12/27/poem/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<blockquote><p><font face='Times new Roman'>by Pablo Neruda</font></p></blockquote><p><font face='Times new Roman'>Tonight I can write the saddest lines.</p><p>Write, for example, ‘The night is starry<br>and the stars are blue and shiver in the distance.’</p><p>The night wind revolves in the sky and sings.</p><p>Tonight I can write the saddest lines.<br>I loved her, and sometimes she loved me too.</p><p>Through nights like this one I held her in my arms.<br>I kissed her again and again under the endless sky.</p><p>She loved me, sometimes I loved her too.<br>How could one not have loved her great still eyes.</p><p>Tonight I can write the saddest lines.<br>To think that I do not have her. To feel that I have lost her.</p><p>To hear the immense night, still more immense without her.<br>And the verse falls to the soul like dew to the pasture.</p><p>What does it matter that my love could not keep her.<br>The night is starry and she is not with me.</p><p>This is all. In the distance someone is singing. In the distance.<br>My soul is not satisfied that it has lost her.</p><p>My sight tries to find her as though to bring her closer.<br>My heart looks for her, and she is not with me.</p><p>The same night whitening the same trees.<br>We, of that time, are no longer the same.</p><p>I no longer love her, that’s certain, but how I loved her.<br>My voice tries to find the wind to touch her hearing.</p><p>Another’s. She will be another’s. As she was before my kisses.<br>Her voice, her bright body. Her infinite eyes.</p><p>I no longer love her, that’s certain, but maybe I love her.<br>Love is so short, forgetting is so long.</p><p>Because through nights like this one I held her in my arms<br>my soul is not satisfied that it has lost her.</p><p>Though this be the last pain that she makes me suffer<br>and these the last verses that I write for her.<br></font></p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>诗文杂选</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>诗文</tag>
      
      <tag>聂鲁达</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
