<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>poem</title>
    <link href="/2023/12/27/poem/"/>
    <url>/2023/12/27/poem/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<hr><h2 id="title-Tonight-I-Can-Write-by-Pablo-Neruda"><a href="#title-Tonight-I-Can-Write-by-Pablo-Neruda" class="headerlink" title="title: Tonight I Can Write by Pablo Neruda"></a>title: Tonight I Can Write by Pablo Neruda</h2><p>Tonight I can write the saddest lines.</p><p>Write, for example, ‘The night is starry<br>and the stars are blue and shiver in the distance.’</p><p>The night wind revolves in the sky and sings.</p><p>Tonight I can write the saddest lines.<br>I loved her, and sometimes she loved me too.</p><p>Through nights like this one I held her in my arms.<br>I kissed her again and again under the endless sky.</p><p>She loved me, sometimes I loved her too.<br>How could one not have loved her great still eyes.</p><p>Tonight I can write the saddest lines.<br>To think that I do not have her. To feel that I have lost her.</p><p>To hear the immense night, still more immense without her.<br>And the verse falls to the soul like dew to the pasture.</p><p>What does it matter that my love could not keep her.<br>The night is starry and she is not with me.</p><p>This is all. In the distance someone is singing. In the distance.<br>My soul is not satisfied that it has lost her.</p><p>My sight tries to find her as though to bring her closer.<br>My heart looks for her, and she is not with me.</p><p>The same night whitening the same trees.<br>We, of that time, are no longer the same.</p><p>I no longer love her, that’s certain, but how I loved her.<br>My voice tries to find the wind to touch her hearing.</p><p>Another’s. She will be another’s. As she was before my kisses.<br>Her voice, her bright body. Her infinite eyes.</p><p>I no longer love her, that’s certain, but maybe I love her.<br>Love is so short, forgetting is so long.</p><p>Because through nights like this one I held her in my arms<br>my soul is not satisfied that it has lost her.</p><p>Though this be the last pain that she makes me suffer<br>and these the last verses that I write for her.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
